We're not peeping, are we?
我说  我们这该不会是在偷窥吧
Shut up and just look!
闭上嘴看就是了
It's about to begin.
就快要开始了
Peeping right early in the morning.
一大清早就在偷窥
What an elegant taste, kids.
还真是高雅的兴趣啊  小鬼们
So, sorry...
对对对不起
Well
那个
We just want to pick up the changes on the road.
我们只是想捡掉在地上的零钱而已
If you just admitted it,
如果你们老实承认
I might have let you have a look in there.
我原本还可以让你们看看呢
Really?
真的吗
So?
怎么样
Do you wanna be a hypocrite,
是要当一个伪善者呢
or an honest boy?
还是当一个诚实的人呢
I... I want to...
我…我想…
Just kidding!
开玩笑的
Don't be so nervous.
别这么紧张兮兮的
Underwear being revealed is like the shooting stars.
内裤走光和流星一样
They have their value because they are hard to be seen.
就是难得一见才有它的价值
Don't stare at the bottom when you are walking.
走路别老盯着下面看
look up, kids.
也抬头向上看看吧  少年
Look up?
向上看吗
The goddess does exist, right?
女神真的是存在的吧
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Episode 7 "zero-sum game"
第七话「零和游戏」
Recently in the Saitama region,
最近在埼玉地区
both the company and the school have seen an increase in the absence rate.
不管是公司还是学校  都出现了缺席率上升的问题
Those who are being absent said that,
缺席的人都表示
They didn't want to get up because of their wonderful dream.
因为梦境太美好起不了床
Now we are seeking solutions to deal with it as soon as possible.
目前正在找寻早期解决的方法
Dream?
梦?
The teacher overslept, so he will be late. You will have self-study class.
老师睡过头迟到 本节课改自习
The teachers overslept.
连老师都睡过头了
Not just the teachers.
不是只有老师而已
Is it...
难道说…
What.
什么
Kirara, the same thing happened in your school?
云母你们的学校也这样啊
That is to say,
那也就是说…
Situations in our schools are the same?
大家的学校也一样吗
Everyone said they dreamed of what they want
大家都说梦见了自己想做的梦
and they had a good time in their dreams.
在梦中过得很快乐
I heard that some people would be sleeping all day because of that.
听说还有人因为这样一整天都在睡觉
It might because
这说不定是…
when people dream about what they want,
让人类梦见理想中的梦境
they can get away from the cruel reality.
使人逃避现实
And that will make people weaker. Something has this power.
借此让人类衰退的能力持有者
It could be Maboroshi Chuu's doing.
这可能是幻梦虫搞的鬼
I always wonder
我每次都在想
why they keep beating about the bush.
她们的能力怎么都这么拐弯抹角啊
Of course we would.
这是当然的
In the beginning, we want to
我们原本就是
invade using peaceful approach.
希望以和平手段进行侵略的种族
But since the queen got missed,
但是自从女王行踪不明后
it seemed to be out of control.
似乎就开始失去控制了
Things will get worse if we don't think of something to stop this.
不想点办法解决就糟了
We have to stop them ASAP.
我们得快点阻止她们
To reach this goal,
为了这个目的
let's get some H-energy first, Kirara.
先来一起储存满满的H能源吧  云母
Wait...
等一下…
Tya Tya, Stop...
茶茶  不可以…
Stop messing around with me!
你们不要闹了啦
According to maps uncle sent us,
从叔叔送来的地图资料看来
We're here.
应该就是这里没错了
It does look like the place where Kisei Chuu would hide.
的确很像是规制虫会潜伏的地方
It is kind of creepy.
有点让人毛骨悚然呢
Nice to meet you. I am Maboroshi Chuu.
初次见面  我是幻梦虫
I've been waiting, HXEROS.
我等你们很久了  HXEROS
You are here, too
看来您也在那里呢
Her Majesty, our "former" princess
「前」公主陛下
I think you will be disappointed at the humans,
想必接下来您一定会对人类失望
and regret betraying us.
并且对背叛我们感到后悔的
Stop the nonsense. Come out.
少说废话  快点给我出来
Someones has too much H-energy here.
这里有人H能源存太多
She can't wait to beat you!
现在已经快受不了了
Stop...
别说了
I know what you were doing.
而且你从刚才就在搞什么鬼
You were not speaking to us through the brain,
弄得好像是从脑内对我们说话似的
but just by the microphone.
结果明明只是用麦克风讲的嘛
All right.
好吧
Let's fight right now.
那我们现在就立刻开始战斗吧
What's wrong?
怎么了
The enemy in the deepest mind
存在于自身内心深处的敌人
is your biggest enemy called "desire".
名为「欲望」的最强大的敌人
I... What happened?
我…到底是…
Retto.
小烈
Hoshino.
星乃
Didn't we agree that we call each other by the name?
我们不是说好要叫彼此的名字了吗
Is that so?
是这样吗
You are a bad boy.
你好过分喔
We have been being in relationship.
我们明明都已经在交往了
Or
不然
if you can answer to my question,
只要你答对我现在出的问题
I will forgive you.
我就原谅你
Now, say 10 times of "kiss".
你先说十次Kiss看看
Why?
为什么要我讲这个
Just do it.
你讲就是了
All right.
我知道了啦
Kiss…
Kiss…
Here comes the question.
那我要问问题啰
Starting with 'S' and ending with 'Ki'
S开头  Ki结尾
What did you say before you said kiss?
在Kiss之前会说的词是什么呢
What kind of question is that?
这算哪门子的问题啊
Look at me while answering.
要好好看着我回答喔
S …
S…
Love
喜欢
Nope
答错了
The answer is striped bass.
答案是鲈鱼
The correct answer is striped bass in the order of the family Saccharidae
正确答案是鲈鱼目鱚科的鲈鱼
Why does your face turn red?
你的脸怎么变红了
You misunderstand something?
你是不是误会成什么了
Who answer that kind of question?
这种问题谁猜得出来啊
The second question is...
那么第二个问题
I am gonna to do.
我现在准备要做的
the thing that starts with 'Ki' and ends with 'S'.
Ki开头S结尾的事情…
What is it?
是什么呢
I really love
原来我真的很喜欢…
this girl.
这个家伙
But which me do you like?
但你喜欢的是哪个我呢
You like the one dating you now,
是现在和你交往的我呢
or the one who was called Iron Virgin
还是人称铁处女的我呢
or the one who you fell in love with in the first time.
难道说是初恋时的我吗
or
还是说
the one when I was a kid.
是幼儿退化时的我吗
Which one of me do you like best?
你最喜欢的是什么样的我呢
Both my mind and my body
不管是内心还是身体
could change as you want.
我都可以随着小烈的想法变化喔
Choose one.
选一个吧
I like
我喜欢的是…
all of you.
你们所有人
I love all of you right here.
我喜欢这里的所有人
Everything about Hoshino.
星乃的所有一切
I like all.
我都喜欢
Yes, before you have changed,
没错  不管是改变以前
He said all of us!
竟然说我们所有人
What a fool!
真是个傻瓜
or after you have changed,
还是改变之后
I want to share my whole life
我要将我今后的人生
with all of Hoshino!
全部奉献给所有的云母
If it is a dream,
如果这是梦的话…
please don't wake up.
拜托不要醒来
Is it here, Moeno？
就是这里吗  萌萎
I can feel the Kisei Chuu.
我感觉到规制虫的气味了
I think there are two of them.
我想应该有两只
Really?
是吗
Finally, I'm in.
总算潜进来了
You are …
你是…
Go back to the reality now.
快点回到现实世界
Get rid of the Maboroshi Chuu
将幻梦虫收拾掉吧
No way!
我不要
I want to stay in this world and take care of them for my whole life.
我要在这边的世界  养她们所有人一辈子
Is this really that good?
这样子真的好吗
This world, simply speaking, is a fantasy of yours.
这里简单说就是烈人的妄想世界
You can only feel the things that you've seen or imagined.
只能体验烈人看过或想像过的事物
But
但是
If I say, after you beat the Maboroshi Chuu,
如果我说你将打倒幻梦虫后
I can make you feel the real Hoshino and get you the experience that you can never imagine...
我就让你感受连真正的云母  都无法让你想像的体验的话呢
That experience...
你说的那个
is it worthy enough for me to give up all of my Hoshinos?
有足以让我舍弃这云母后宫的价值吗
I promise you.
我和你保证
I see.
我知道了
What should I do to come back?
要怎么做才能回去
Put it on and pinch your cheek.
戴上这个捏一下脸颊
I see.
原来如此
Retto,
小烈
Wish me happy even when you go back to that world.
回到那边的世界也要让我幸福喔
Seems like someone is about to wake up from the dream.
看来有一个人快从梦中醒来了
Let's enhance the sleeping wave a little bit.
再稍微强化一下睡眠音波吧
We heard a lot of annoying noise.
真是的  从刚才一直吵得要死
You did it.
原来是你搞的鬼吗
Humans.
人类
Why can't I influence you with my sleeping wave?
为什么我的催眠对你们无效
I seem to have a strange dream. That's for sure.
我好像是有做一个奇怪的梦没错
But I felt nothing.
但我根本一点感觉也没有
You should...
你应该
make me feel something that is much better than a sweet dream, huh?
能让我体验比梦还要更棒的感觉吧
You are awake now, Retto?
你总算醒过来了吗  烈人
Yes,
对了
we were here to beat the Maboroshi Chuu,
我们是过来打倒规制虫的
But were knocked unconscious by the Maboroshi Chuu.
结果被敌人给弄昏了
What's that?
怎么了
The sound comes from there.
声音是从那里传过来的
Hey, wake up!
喂  快起来
That's useless.
不行
You can only go into their dreams to wake them up.
要叫她们起来只能进到梦中
Or, finish the Maboroshi Chuu.
或是将规制虫打倒才行
Shit.
可恶
Ladies, you have to wait for me.
各位  你们要等我啊
You, you are …
你  你们是…
Shiko
紫子
Here is another Kisei Chuu.
那边还有一只规制虫
That one?
就是那个吗
Why do you suddenly attack her?
为什么突然攻击她
Of course for killing her!
还为什么  当然是为了除掉牠啊
The child is with us.
这孩子是我们的同伴
So...
原来如此
You are HXEROS of Saitama Branch
你们就是埼玉支部的HXEROS吗
Let me go!
放开我
Indeed as expected, is this all you can do?
果然就只有这点程度吗
Don't think that you destroyed the base of the Kisei Chuu,
别因为你们摧毁了规制虫的巢穴
you can be proud of yourselves.
就趾高气昂起来了
We will take it with us.
这家伙就由我们接收了
Goodbye!
再见
Wait a minute!
等一下
I said it is our friend.
我说过是我们的同伴了吧
I thought you were knocked out by me.
我还以为应该弄昏你了才对
I didn't expect there would be such a guy in the Saitama Branch.
原来埼玉支部还有这种人吗
Interesting.
真有意思
Oh, I forgot,
也对
this is the boundary between Tokyo and Saitama.
反正这里是东京和埼玉的边界
So whose pray is the Kisei Chuu...
这只规制虫到底是谁的猎物
Let's decide it in a heroic way.
就用像英雄的决斗方式决定吧
I am Kusamura Shiko from HXEROS Tokyo Branch.
我是HXEROS东京支部的丛雨紫子
That's Wakakusa Moeno who speaks with a lisp.
那边那个口齿不清的是若草萌萎
Nice to meet you.
请多指教
The rule is simple.
规则很简单
Who is turned on first
先开始有感觉
and releases the H-energy will lose.
释放出H能源的一方就算输了
Maboroshi Chuu. Make you obsessed with me.
幻梦虫  让你痴迷于我
Use H-energy to slug it out, huh?
你说用H能源一决胜负
Wait... What the hell are you doing?
等…你到底在做什么
What else? This is a zero-sum game.
还做什么  这是零和游戏啊
The one who feels first loses.
先有感觉的一方就算输了
You said we will do it in the HXERO way!
你说像英雄(HXERO)的决斗方式
Is this what you meant?
是这个意思吗
What?
干嘛啊
You are a HXEROS. This should be nothing to you.
既然是HXEROS  这点小事是当然的吧
Don't just lie there,
别光顾着躺在那里
Move!
你也快点动起来啊
I can't move...
动不了
She used the power of XERO GEAR to greatly improve her power.
她用XERO  GEAR的力量  大幅强化了身体能力吗
Huh? Finally fight back?
总算有干劲了吗
Is fighting back the only thing I can do?
只能展开反击了吗
No
不行
I'm in love with Hoshino.
我心中已经有了星乃
I can't do this to other girls.
怎么能对其他女孩子出手
Your master is a herbivorous man?
你的主人是草食系男子吗
We just have to wait to see him lose.
看来他会输也只是时间问题了
Shiko seems to get into it.
紫子看起来已经进入状况了
Retto has been trained by Kirara and others everyday.
每天都在接受云母她们训练的烈人
He won't lose to such degree of seduction.
不会因为那点程度就动摇的
If you go on like this...
再这样下去…
You don't want to surrender, do you?
你不会是想投降了吧
HXEROS in Saitama are so weak and soft...
埼玉的HXEROS还真是窝囊呢
Hoshino...
星乃…
Retto, tomorrow is a holiday.
烈人  明天是假日
We put the child in bed,
我们快点哄孩子睡觉
and... Okay?
然后…好吗?
No, no, no, no, no. The other me.
这可不行喔  另一个我
Retto is in love with
因为烈人喜欢的人
me in this period.
是这个时期的我啊
No …
不…
No!
不行!
Just a dream?
是梦?
Everybody, wake up!
大家快点醒醒啊
What?
干嘛啦
I just had a good dream.
我才做了一个好梦耶
Pity. .
真是的
All right, Enjo, wake up.
好了  炎城你也快点醒醒吧
Strange
奇怪
Enjo?
炎城?
I can't believe you can bear it.
想不到你还挺能忍的嘛
But,
不过
Looks like you are about to reach your limit.
看样子你也已经快到极限了
He can't satisfy Shiko as well?
这个人果然也没办法满足紫子吗
It's not good.
这下不妙了
If they go on like this, Retto... Retto would...
再这样下去烈人…烈人他会…
You can't lose, Retto!
你不可以输  烈人
What's the matter?
怎么了
Come here!
过来
Let me go!
快放开我
HXE RED "Meat status"
HXE  RED  「肉食状态」
It worked!
终于成功了
What's going on …
怎么回事…
I can't take. .
已经…
no more...
不行了
I'm sorry, Shiko.
对不起  紫子
I am no match for him...
我实在不是他的对手…
Looks like you finally take it serious.
看来你总算是认真起来了
The guy is totally different from before.
这家伙现在简直判若两人
But, this guy...
不过如果是这家伙
maybe he can make me feel...
说不定有办法让我有感觉
Your body is very sensitive.
你的身体非常敏感
which means, your whole body is full of erogenous zones.
也就是说全身上下都是性感带
Is there a cure for that?
这治得好吗
It's XERO GEAR.
这个是XERO  GEAR
It can turn your H-energy to power.
是能将人的H能源转换为力量的装置
When the high energy consumption mode is on,
只要切换为高耗能模式
if you have H-energy and release your energy at once,
一旦储存了H能源  就立刻加以释放的话
it should be able to ease your symptoms.
应该就能减轻症状才对
It has a side effect
只是  其伴随的副作用
that your body would be very jaded to outside simulations.
会使身体感度变得极为迟钝
Even so, do you still want to be treated?
即使如此你也还是想治疗吗
I …
我…
Because of my body, I'm always afraid of touching others.
因为这样的体质  一直很害怕和他人接触
But...
但是
I want to touch other kids at my age,
我想和其他同年纪的孩子彼此接触
feel each other's warmness.
感受彼此的温度
Even if the body can no longer be sensitive,
就算身体变得再也无法有感觉
I still don't want my heart to be dull.
我也不希望让心灵也变得迟钝
From that day on,
从那天起
As a HXEROS,
我就以HXEROS一员的身分
I fight with the Kisei Chuu.
与规制虫战斗着
And that sensitive issue is under control because of that.
过度敏感的症状因此获得了控制
But there is no one who can really turn me on.
但能让我真的兴奋起来的人事物  也都不复存在了
Yes,
没错
Until today.
直到今天为止
All the heat. .
这种浑身发热的感觉
and the pulsations in my chest...
胸口高亢的悸动
I hadn't felt that in a long time...
已经多久没感受过了呢
If I can...
要是能就这样
make all the H-energy I have felt...
将至今感觉到的H能源一口气…
released at once, that would be amazing.
全部释放出来的话就好了
It's strange. I was...
奇怪  我刚才到底是…
Are you alright, Shiko?
你没事吧  紫子
Can you believe that we all lost?
没想到我们两个都输给他了
I haven't leaked a drop.
我可是一滴也没有漏出来喔
What are you talking about?
你在说什么啊
I said I lost,
我是说我虽然输了
but I didn't really "let it out"!
但我也没真的「释放」出来啊
Shiko is very adorable when you are turned on.
虽然有感觉的紫子很可爱
But you are also cute when you are nervous!
但慌张的紫子也很可爱呢
What are you talking about, idiot?
你在说什么啊  笨蛋
Hey, wait a minute!
喂  给我等一下
Yes?
是
What's your name?
你叫什么名字
Retto.
烈人
My name is Retto Enjo.
我叫炎城烈人
Luckily you got his name.
幸好有问到他的名字呢
Shut up!
吵死了
There is another Kisei Chuu. I can smell it.
还有一只规制虫的味道
You guys are not strong enough!
你们下手下得不够重啊
HXEROS with no H-energy -Shiko!
没有H能源的HXEROS -紫子
are just ordinary people.
不过只是个普通人类
I want you to sleep forever.
我要让你们永远沉睡下去
Do you really think you can get away from my grasp?
你们以为能逃得过  我幻梦虫的手掌心吗
Everyone
大家
The Light of the Sky!
「天空的闪光」
Lamaze Cannon!
「拉玛泽砲」
Where are you touching, asshole!
你手在摸哪里啊  混蛋
You just did that to me!
刚才明明才对我做了那种事
Are you all right, Enjo?
你没事吧  炎城
Is everyone all right?
大家也都平安无事吗
They are?
这些人是?
They are HXEORS from the Tokyo Branch.
那两个人好像是东京支部的HXEORS
Moeno!
萌萎
Momoka!
阿百
You guys know each other?
你们认识吗
We were in the same school before.
我们同所国中
I moved to Tokyo because I was admitted to a private high school.
因为我考上私立高中  所以搬家到东京去了
You haven't change a bit.
阿百好像一点也没变呢
What do you mean by that?
你是看哪里讲的啦
So,
怎么样
You still want to take Tya Tya away?
你们现在还打算把茶茶抢走吗
Listen,
我先声明
I won't give up.
我可没有就此放弃
You will be mine!
我绝对会让你成为我的东西
Keep that in your mind!
给我记住
Goodbye.
再见
You seems to become the target of a terrible girl.
你好像被不得了的家伙盯上了呢
Tya Tya.
茶茶
So, what happened?
所以  结果到底发生什么事了
I don't remember it clearly.
我已经没有什么印象了
But,
不过
Retto is really impressive when he becomes a beast!
变成野兽的烈人真让人刮目相看呢
Stop it.
这你就不用说了啦
You will be mine!
我绝对会让你成为我的东西
Keep that in your mind!
给我记住
That means you, Retto Enjo.
那句话是对你说的  炎城烈人
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Next Episode "H-Energy☆Monster"
下一回「H能量☆怪兽」